The One Where It All Began
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
There's nothing to tell.
It's just some guy I work with.
You're going out with a guy.
There's gotta be something
wrong with him.
All right, Joey, be nice.
So does he have a hump
and a hair piece?
Wait. Does he eat chalk?
I don't want her to go
through what I did with Carl.
Okay, everybody relax.
Relax. This is not even a date.
It's just two people going out to
dinner and not having sex.
Sounds like a date to me.
I'm in high school,
in the middle of the cafeteria. . .
. . .and I realize I'm totally naked.
I've had that dream.
Then I look down and I realize
there is a phone. . .
. . .there.
-Instead of--
-That's right!
That one, I've never had.
All of a sudden,
the phone starts to ring.
I don't know what to do.
Everybody's looking at me.
They weren't looking at you before?
Finally, I figure
I'd better answer it.
And it turns out it's my mother.
Which is very, very weird
because she never calls me.
This guy says, ''Hello,''
I wanna kill myself.
You okay, sweetie?
www.tvsubtitles.net